{
    "quiz": [
        {
            "question": "How do you prompt users with messages and at the same time requesting user inputs?",
            "answer": [
                "alert()",
                "display()",
                "prompt()",
                "confirm()"
            ],
            "correct": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is the minimum browser version that supports JavaScript?",
            "answer": [
                "Navigator v2.0",
                "Mozilla V1.5",
                "IE 2.0",
                "Navigator V1.0"
            ],
            "correct": "0"
        },
        {
            "question": "With the DATE object, which of the following allows you to call a function based on an elapsed time?",
            "answer": [
                "setElapsedTime()",
                "Timeout()",
                "setTimeout()",
                "setTime()"
            ],
            "correct": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "You want to design a form validation mechanism. Using String methods, which of the following are the steps involved?",
            "answer": [
                "Check for the presence of certain characters",
                "Check the position of substrings",
                "Test the length of data",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following correctly describe the relationship of JavaScript and 'objects'?",
            "answer": [
                "JavaScript is Object-oriented",
                "JavaScript is Object-based",
                "JavaScript is Object-driven",
                "JavaScript has no relationship with objects"
            ],
            "correct": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following do you use for a multi-way branch?",
            "answer": [
                "if",
                "if then",
                "if else",
                "switch"
            ],
            "correct": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is used to restart the inner most loop?",
            "answer": [
                "abort",
                "breakloop",
                "stop",
                "continue label"
            ],
            "correct": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax of FOR?",
            "answer": [
                "for (increment; initialize; test)",
                "for (initialize; test; increment)",
                "for (test; initialize; incremenet)",
                "for (test; increment; initialize)"
            ],
            "correct": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you find out which character occurs at the 5th position in a string 'How are you'?",
            "answer": [
                "substring()",
                "string()",
                "stringLength()",
                "charAt()"
            ],
            "correct": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following are the advantages of using JavaScript for form validation?",
            "answer": [
                "increase end-user satisfaction",
                "increase validity of form submission",
                "conservation of bandwidth",
                "all of the above"
            ],
            "correct": "3"
        }
    ]
}